Hold your head up straight. 把頭抬起來
Yes, like that. 對，就這樣
One, two, three
一、二、三
Ok, great. 好，很好
Now we'll change the background.
現在我們要換背景了
Go and change it. 請幫我換背景
OK. 好的
Gently does it.
小心一點喔
Yes, that's good.
好 這樣很好
Is that OK? 這樣可以嗎？
It's fine. 嗯嗯可以
OK, everyone, look this way.
好了各位，請看這邊
Hey, little boy, over here!
哈囉！小男生看這邊喔！
One, two, three.
一、二、三
OK, that's good.
嗯，這樣好
Now for the next lot. 好換下一組人
Come on. 來吧
Print out their photo for them.
記得把照片洗給他們
OK.
好的
Here, this is for the photo
這是拍照的答謝
Right then
好的
Two... 兩張...
And this... 還有這些...
That makes 17. 這樣就17了
Come on, let's go. 好了，我們走吧
Ah, the stool.
阿，有凳子。
17 yuan, it's expensive! 17元！好貴唷
Petrol, paper, ink. Everything's gone up.
石油，紙，墨水，什麼都漲了。
OK, I'm ready.
好，我準備好了喔。
Everything except incomes!
什麼都漲就是薪水沒漲！
Shall we do it, then?
我們開始吧，好嗎？
No, wait. You two change places.
等一下喔，你們倆交換一下
You there and you here.
你去那邊 你在這邊
We can't see you… That's better.
我們看不到你...這樣好多了
That's it.
對，就這樣
Shall we do it?
可以開始了嗎？
Hurry up!
快一點！
Oh, him too.
喔，還有他。
Take his work jacket off.
把他的外套脫掉
Give that here.
這放這邊。
- How's this? 這樣可以嗎？
- Yes, it's better. 嗯好多了
Ah, the little one.
阿，還有小朋友
Careful now, be gentle.
阿小心點唷！小心小心
Hold him tight.
抓緊他
Maybe not that tight. 不要這麼緊好了
No, not like that. 不，不是這樣
Gently and higher up. 輕輕的然後往上
That’s good. 這樣好
Everyone, look over here.
好了，大家看這邊
One, two, three
一、二、三
Grandaad.
外公
-Can you wear this? 可以請您穿這個嘛？
-Yes 好阿
- Can you try it for size? 你可以試一下尺寸嘛？
- It'll be fine. 沒關係啦
A top-of-the-range jacket!
鑽石高檔外套！
There.
好多了
Here, son, can you wear this? 那兒子可以請你穿這個嘛？
Try it on. 試試看
Or, if not that...
呃...那不要這件...
Herem have this one.
繼承人我們穿這件好嗎？
Gongbo! Gongbo...
Too bad for him. Come back.
他在幹什麼，叫他回來
It doesn't matter. 沒關係的
Stand there. OK, that's good. 好那我們站這邊
Everyone, look at me. 大家看我這邊
Little one, look over here. 小朋友看過來唷
Look at me!
看我！
This way.
看這邊
One, two, three.
一、二、三
- Where did you get the beads?
你在哪找到這些珠珠阿？
- Lhassa. 拉薩
Youngsters don't wear old clothes
any more, like the kid earlier.
現在很少有年輕人像剛剛那位願意穿傳統服飾了
His mother made it for him.
Now she's dead, he always wears it.
那件是他媽媽做的，他媽死後他總是穿那件
Help me with this tie, my friend. 朋友，可以幫我一下嗎？
OK. 沒問題
Come on. 來吧
The knot should be inside. There.
這結要在裡面，好了
- How's that? 可以嗎？
- Perfect. 很好
A bit more this way. 再過來一點點
And you, in the middle. 然後你，站中間
The flower. 那個花
Now, both of you, look over here.
好，現在兩位都看這邊
Look over here. 看這裡
Hey! 嘿！
- Mr Mayor, a cigarette? 市長！抽煙嗎？
- No, thanks. 不用了
As you're all here, 既然你們都在，
I have some announcements. 我有事情要宣布
For the New Socialist Campaign,
the authorities will be visiting us.
為了新社會主義運動，當局要來探訪我們
Everyone must clean their home, 每個人
inside and out. 都要把家裡打掃徹底
Also, a sacred yak belonging 另外 Lahmo 有隻
to Lahmo Tso has been stolen. 神聖的蝥牛被偷了
There must be strangers around.
這裡一定有陌生人，我們會調查的
We'll investigate it.
Goodbye! 再見！
Wait! 等一下！
Come and sit here. 你坐過來。
- The motorbike's a good idea. 摩托車是個好點子
- Yes, it’s brand-new. 對阿！這全新的
There's a flower there. 這裡有束花
Put it on the motorbike. 把它放在摩托車上吧
- You have lots of props. 你好多道具喔
- It's my job. 這是我的工作
- You like that? 你喜歡嗎？
- Yes. 喜歡
Knot it underneath. 在下面打結吧
Perfect. 太棒了
Look over here, both of you.
來，兩個人都看這邊
And smile. That's it.
笑一個，很好
One, two, three.
一、二、三
Hey, clear off!
嘿！清場清場！
Hold it in your hand.
把它拿好
You too, hold it like that.
你也是，這樣拿著
Look over here.
來，看這邊
Over here!
看這邊！
One, two...
一、二...
- No, don't! 不要！
- Don’t take it off him. 別把它拿走
Don't do that again. 不要再這樣了喔
Look over here. 看這邊
Keep still. 不要動
One, two, three.
一、二、三
Come on, clear off!
好了！清場！
You too, over here!
你也是，看這邊！
Go and look at yourself 快去看
on the photos. 去看你的照片
- Ah, here's Grandma! 阿！這是奶奶！
- Yes. 是阿
This is Ama Lhamo Tso. 這是 Ama
I mentioned her earlier. 我們剛剛有提過她
She's never 她從來沒有拍過照片
been photographed before.
- We'll make it special. 我們會拍一張很棒的
- Do you have other backgrounds?
你還有其他的背景嗎？
Of course. 當然
Bring the catalogue. 幫我把目錄拿來
- Come and see. 你來看看
- OK. 好的
- This one? 這個呢？
- It's nice, but not for her. 這不錯，但不適合她
- Or this? 還是這個呢？
- Yes, that's good. 嗯！這個好
Lower that one. 把這降下來
- The motorbike was nice of you. 謝謝你的摩托車
- It was no big deal. 這沒什麼
- What village are you from? 你是哪個村子來的？
- I'm from here. 我就是這邊來的
How many people live in the village?
有多少人住在這個村莊？
- 248 households. 有248戶
- That's a lot. 哇那很多耶
But the youngsters 但是年輕人
all go off to town to work. 都跑出村莊工作了
- How's that? 這樣怎麼樣？
- Yes, perfect. 嗯，很好
It's her dream 有一天去看看布達拉宮
to visit Potala Palace one day. 是她的夢想
When the road's finished 等路蓋好
it'll be easier to get here. 就會比較方便過去的
Yes, we'll save over ten hours.
對阿！會省下十個小時耶
- When will it be finished? 什麼時候會蓋好呢？
- By spring. 這個春天
Oh, no, she's prostrating herself!
喔不！她自己膜拜了起來
Up you get, Grandma. 奶奶起來吧
Here, I'll take your prayer wheel.
來，我幫你拿轉經輪
Help her to get up. 扶她起來吧
That's good. 嗯好了
- Now sit down here. 好，坐這邊
- And look that way.現在看這裡喔
- Yes, this way. 對，看這邊
- You have to look that way. 你要看這邊唷
This way! 這邊！
- You'll have to change the photo.
你趕快換一下照片好了
- Yes, change it. 對，換一下好了
That's better, the ocean. 這樣好多了，海洋阿
- The other way… 另外一邊...
- You have to look the other way. 你要看另一邊唷
Look at me, look at me. 看著我，看著我
Yes, look at him. 對，看著他
One, two, three.
一、二、三
Shall I put the rolls in the truck?
要把這一卷放在卡車上嗎？
Hang on, we'll take this one first.
等一下，我們先把這個拿走
Make sure it's well rolled first.
確定它有捲好了喔
Put it here for now.
把它放在這邊
Pack the clothes away now.
把衣服也收一收
Hey, kid, how are you?
哈囉，孩子你還好嗎？
- Are you passing by Lhassa? 你會經過拉薩嗎？
- Yes. 會阿
Take this butter to Potala Palace, 經過布達拉宮時
as an offering for my mother. 把這奶油貢給我媽
- Yes, I promise I'll do it. 好，我保證我會
- Thank you. 謝謝你
- Have you got all the props. 你把道具都拿齊了嗎
- Yeah, got them. 嗯都好了
Put them away tidily, 把它們放整齊了，
so they're ready when we need them.
這樣我們需要的時候才好找。
There, that's good. 嗯，這樣好
- Where do I put them all? 這些應該放哪邊？
- In a box, so they don't break. 拿個盒子才不會破
We'd better hurry 我們動作要快一點
before they block the road. 趕在他們封路以前
- Why are they working at night? 他們為什麼晚上工作阿？
- To be ready for the authorities. 就為了當局囉
- Shall we stop in Kang Ba to sleep?
要在康巴暫停睡覺嗎？
- Yes. 嗯
- We mustn't forget the kid's butter.
那個孩子的奶油千萬別忘
- No, no. 不會的