Hold your head up straight.
Yes, like that.
One, two, three
Ok, great.
Now we'll change the background.
Go and change it.
OK.
Gently does it.
Yes, that's good.
Is that OK?
It's fine.
OK, everyone, look this way.
Hey, little boy, over here!
One, two, three.
OK, that's good.
Now for the next lot.
Come on.
Print out their photo for them.
OK.
Here, this is for the photo
Right then
Two...
And this...
That makes 17.
Come on, let's go.
Ah, the stool.
17 yuan, it's expensive!
Petrol, paper, ink. Everything's gone up.
OK, I'm ready.
Everything except incomes!
Shall we do it, then?
No, wait. You two change places.
You there and you here.
We can't see you… That's better.
That's it.
Shall we do it?
Hurry up!
Oh, him too.
Take his work jacket off.
Give that here.
- How's this?
- Yes, it's better.
Ah, the little one.
Careful now, be gentle.
Hold him tight.
Maybe not that tight.
No, not like that.
Gently and higher up.
That’s good.
Everyone, look over here.
One, two, three
Grandaad.
-Can you wear this?
-Yes
- Can you try it for size?
- It'll be fine.
A top-of-the-range jacket!
There.
Here, son, can you wear this?
Try it on.
Or, if not that...
Herem have this one.
Gongbo! Gongbo...
Too bad for him. Come back.
It doesn't matter.
Stand there. OK, that's good.
Everyone, look at me.
Little one, look over here.
Look at me!
This way.
One, two, three.
- Where did you get the beads?
- Lhassa.
Youngsters don't wear old clothes
any more, like the kid earlier.
His mother made it for him.
Now she's dead, he always wears it.
Help me with this tie, my friend.
OK.
Come on.
The knot should be inside. There.
- How's that?
- Perfect.
A bit more this way.
And you, in the middle.
The flower.
Now, both of you, look over here.
Look over here.
Hey!
- Mr Mayor, a cigarette?
- No, thanks.
As you're all here,
I have some announcements.
For the New Socialist Campaign,
the authorities will be visiting us.
Everyone must clean their home,
inside and out.
Also, a sacred yak belonging
to Lahmo Tso has been stolen.
There must be strangers around.
We'll investigate it.
Goodbye!
Wait!
Come and sit here.
- The motorbike's a good idea.
- Yes, it’s brand-new.
There's a flower there.
Put it on the motorbike.
- You have lots of props.
- It's my job.
- You like that?
- Yes.
Knot it underneath.
Perfect.
Look over here, both of you.
And smile. That's it.
One, two, three.
Hey, clear off!
Hold it in your hand.
You too, hold it like that.
Look over here.
Over here!
One, two...
- No, don't!
- Don’t take it off him.
Don't do that again.
Look over here.
Keep still.
One, two, three.
Come on, clear off!
You too, over here!
Go and look at yourself
on the photos.
- Ah, here's Grandma!
- Yes.
This is Ama Lhamo Tso.
I mentioned her earlier.
She's never
been photographed before.
- We'll make it special.
- Do you have other backgrounds?
Of course.
Bring the catalogue.
- Come and see.
- OK.
- This one?
- It's nice, but not for her.
- Or this?
- Yes, that's good.
Lower that one.
- The motorbike was nice of you.
- It was no big deal.
- What village are you from?
- I'm from here.
How many people live in the village?
- 248 households.
- That's a lot.
But the youngsters
all go off to town to work.
- How's that?
- Yes, perfect.
It's her dream
to visit Potala Palace one day.
When the road's finished
it'll be easier to get here.
Yes, we'll save over ten hours.
- When will it be finished?
- By spring.
Oh, no, she's prostrating herself!
Up you get, Grandma.
Here, I'll take your prayer wheel.
Help her to get up.
That's good.
- Now sit down here.
- And look that way.
- Yes, this way.
- You have to look that way.
This way!
- You'll have to change the photo.
- Yes, change it.
That's better, the ocean.
- The other way…
- You have to look the other way.
Look at me, look at me.
Yes, look at him.
One, two, three.
Shall I put the rolls in the truck?
Hang on, we'll take this one first.
Make sure it's well rolled first.
Put it here for now.
Pack the clothes away now.
Hey, kid, how are you?
- Are you passing by Lhassa?
- Yes.
Take this butter to Potala Palace,
as an offering for my mother.
- Yes, I promise I'll do it.
- Thank you.
- Have you got all the props.
- Yeah, got them.
Put them away tidily,
so they're ready when we need them.
There, that's good.
- Where do I put them all?
- In a box, so they don't break.
We'd better hurry
before they block the road.
- Why are they working at night?
- To be ready for the authorities.
- Shall we stop in Kang Ba to sleep?
- Yes.
- We mustn't forget the kid's butter.
- No, no.