What is that?
Well, I just thought it would be good to start with like, a quote or something.
Don't...., get rid of it, Idiot.
Ladies and gentlemen, hello welcome to the Wednesday
night open mic at the egg and sparrow
we've a very special treat for you this evening,
a chap giving his debut performance,
so please put your hands together and
welcome onto the stage.... Mr Tom Moody.
I'm Tom Moody.....
And... Well. What?
Well, we can't both tell this..
Absolutely, let me, I'm Tom Moody and
this was the moment I knew for sure
I was a deluded fool with no tal....
NO , that’s not true... I am Tom Moody
and I've always loved making music.
even as a little boy me and my cousin Steve would
get together and make recordings of our songs....
Oh please, the only thing Steve and
me ever recorded is ourselves farting.
Other than mums affair with the ice cream
man my childhood was entirely unremarkable.
I was a dull and talentless child, I thank god that
dad was there to rescue me from the last shambles
that me and Steve made of playing live
- Were the... the, ... witches of ...Halloween oooo , ooo, the....
scaryest you've ever seen,
- now to the G,
- we creep, cree....
TO THE G CHORD!, oh for goodness sake, give it to me...
we sneak up in the night and
give you such a FRIGHT!.....
We are the witches of Halloween...
- Yes, but, we were ill prepared that time
- So, what's, that
We've had 32 years of practice since then,
we can turn this around....
I don't want to turn.....
Steve's the best keyboard player
since flipping... Stevie wonder...
- Are you joking...
- Lets make it Big...
- No!
- What about David Bowie?
- What about David Bowie!
- We could really rock them this time!
It never sounded like this...
This is ridiculous...
We don't have a guitar like that....
There were never any strings...
There was no one playing drums!
We never had backing singers...
and Steve doesn't wear leopard skin pants.
That's the thing about talent,
you've either got it, or you've not...
Boring, in fact it's not just boring it's sad,
you actually inspire sadness in people,
you bring people down....
Moron, utter moron
Ha! Ha,You should be ashamed,
Why would anybody want to hear
SHUT UP!
I told you this was pointless, ruined it...
Shut up, please just shut up, or I’m going to
- Oh yeah, what you going to what?
- I'm going to...
Get off me.
You!
Tom,I didn't know...
Tom?
What is it Tom?
I don't want us to sing.
Why?
People will think we're stupid and boring.
Well, I don't think we're stupid and boring,
and we don't have to do it for them,
we can just, do it for us.
Do we have to sing the witches of Halloween?
We don't ever have to sing the witches of Halloween.
- Ok
- Like a bird, is born with a song,
and like a song, wants to be sung...