Fabric and vinyl upholstery jobs!
Your trusted upholsterer
picks up furniture from your house...
and delivers it back to you.
Get your estimate without obligation!
Attention!
Guaranteed results and great discounts!
The upholsterer's truck
has come to town!
Get your estimate without obligation!
We upholster all types of furniture:
chairs, three-seater sofas...
OUT OF ORDER
Paco! You too? Out partying?
C'mon, mate!
Mari Tere told me...
she went to the pines
at the beach...
with Antonio and their little one,
José Manuel.
They saw a light in the distance
and went to see what it was.
As they got closer...
there was this smell of flowers
that became stronger.
They got to the rocks
in the pine grove.
It was all lit up.
They saw the figure
of the Virgin Mary in the light.
Mari Tere says...
that the Virgin
pointed at José Manuel.
She was like that for a while,
then the lights disappeared.
She says that night...
the Virgin got into her son's body.
And they've found out...
if you put your ear
to the back of his neck,
you can hear the Virgin talk.
Don't threaten me! Don't!
Don't you dare!
How's things, Mari Carmen?
Getting by, Trini.
Your turn to clean the stairs
this week?
Yes.
NUCLEUS
OUTER SPACE:
STARS, PLANETS AND SPACESHIPS
The mystery of the Virgin is
that she appears differently...
depending on who she talks to.
Me, I hear a young girl.
Others hear an old lady.
She can speak in Valencian...
But she's always like a mother...
and you sort of feel safe,
listening to her.
She gives you kitchen recipes,
tips for the home,
she tells you
what shops have discounts...
One day she told me:
40,099.
She just kept saying that.
So, I went to the newsagent's...
and saw that number there
on a lottery ticket.
I bought it...
but I didn't win nothing at all.
He wouldn't let me see other guys!
He won't leave me alone!
He claims you had sex with him...
STAIRS CLEANIN SHIFT
MON, TUES, WED, FRI
It's true!
You shut up, liar!
It's hot already.
Too hot.
Tomorrow's going to be even hotter.
And tomorrow's Saturday.
Trini!
Mum!
Mari Carmen,
This letter is for José Vicente...
and for my José Luis,
who cannot read.
Don't try to find me
or worry about me.
It's hard to say good-bye.
But I'm really excited...
about what's going to happen to me.
What lives inside Mari Tere's son...
isn't the Virgin,
no matter what people say.
It's someone from far away.
And he told me...
that he can take me to his planet.
A million miles from Earth.
I had two dreams in life:
having cats
and travelling into space.
The first one can't be
as I'm allergic.
As for my other dream,
this miracle's happened.
I'm really going to miss you.
I might see you from above.
I'm not sure.
But just in case, be good.
I've left lots of food for you.
With all my love.
MYSTERY