Sally!
Be good. 要乖乖的喔
Where are you going? 你要去哪裡？
I have to get some cigarettes for my dad.
我要幫我爸買煙
Hurry then Julien. 那你要快點唷！
We have a test this morning. 我們今天早上有小考
By the way, are your parents coming
對了，你父母週五會來我們的教室會議嘛？
to the class meeting on Friday?
Hurry up! 動作快點唷！
Put your seatbelt on, please. 請繫好安全帶。
Did you get my cigaretters? 你有幫我買煙嘛？
Thanks. 謝啦
Hi Miriam. 嗨 Miriam
Didier, can I leave the kids with you?
Didier, 我可以請你幫我看一下孩子們嗎？
- What's going on? 怎麼了？
- I won't be long. 我不會去太久
Of course. 好阿沒問題
What's the rush?
你在趕什麼？
Register 2 at noon, register 3...
兩輛車登記在中午，三...
- Alarm didn't go off? 警報器沒有關嗎？
- Car trouble again. 又是車子問題
I need to talk to Gaëlle. 我必須和Gaëlle談談
- Hang on. 請等一下
- Can I talk to you a minute? 我可以跟你說一下話嗎？
Sorry. 不好意思， 我請Rofia接著幫您處理。
I'm handing you over to Rofia.
There's a void at Fatou’s register.
Fatou的預約有部分無效
- Ask Robocop. 你問一下 Robocop
- She's not in yet. 她還沒進來
I'll be quick. Wait for me here.
我很快回來，在這裡等我
- In the locker room? 在置物櫃那邊
- OK. 好的
What's going on? 到底怎麼了？
- I need to see Savelli. 我需要見見Savelli
- He's in a meeting. 他正在開會
- I brought the kids. 我把孩子們也帶來了
- What? 什麼？
I don't know what to do. 我不知道該怎麼辦
I must get out quick. 我很快就要走了
It's going to be fine. 一切都會沒事的
It's not a big deal. 沒什麼大不了的
Ask Rofia. 喂？ 你問 Rofia好不好
I have to do something. 我有事情要處理
You choose... It's simple.
換你選...這很簡單的
You choose... Wait, I'll show you.
從這邊選...等等，我給你看
Choose a weapon: a sword...
選一個武器：一把劍嗎...
Hi kids. 哈囉孩子們
Everything alright, Didier? 一切都還好嗎？Didier
Great.
都很好
And that's your score.
然後這是你的分數
She has a fever.
她在發燒。
I'm waiting for the doctor. 我還在等醫生的回覆
I'll let you know. 我會讓你知道
Thank you. Bye. 謝謝，掰掰
Ah... Miriam. 阿..Miriam.
Tell them I'll only be a minute.
告訴他們我很快就回來
I'm sorry to take your time. 我很抱歉佔用你的時間
It's short notice but Gaëlle explained. 我的確剛剛才知道但Gaëlle告訴我了， 我們該怎麼做？
How shall we proceed?
I have no idea. 我也不知道
Do you want to take some time? 你需要一些時間嗎？
Maybe a leave? 也許請假一段時間？
No that's impossible I can't come back after all that…
不這不可能，這種事發生後我之後不可能再回來了
- Have you pressed charges? 你提出告訴了沒？
- No. 沒有
You should press charges.
你應該要提告
You'll need a medical certificate
for your file. 你需要診斷書，為你以後的日子
It's just that... 只是...
I've got the kids 我帶著孩子們和我一起
and we must leave quickly. 而且我們得趕快走了
It would be great, 那很理想
but I don't have time. 但我已經沒有時間了
I see. 我知道了
You're really leaving then? 所以你真的要離開了？
I'm in no rush to see you go!
我還沒準備好看你離開呢！
I can fire you 我可以把你開除
so you get your benefits. 這樣你還是會有一些津貼
But you'll have to come back
for an interview. 但是你必須先回來完成一次面談
Yes, I know. 嗯我知道
Do you have a new address?
你有新的地址了嗎？
I'm leaving town, 我要先離開這個城了
until things calm down. 先等事情比較緩和下來
I don't know where I'm going yet.
我還不知道我要去哪
We have two moths to do the interview.
我們有兩個月可以做這個面談
That's great... 那很好...
It's just... I'm sorry but... 只是... 嗯,不好意思但是..
if I have to wait... 如果我還要等...
What I mean is... 我的意思是...
I'm going to need money. 我很快就需要錢...
No it's fine... 沒關係...
I'll give you my parents' address.
我給你我父母的地址
Accounting will give you an advance.
會計會給你其他建議
You can unblock the interest
on your shared profits.
你可以重新申請想要分你的財產
- For the rest, we'll do like we said.
其他的部份我們會像剛剛說的去做
- Thank you. 謝謝你們
I need to open my own account.
我需要開一個我自己的帳戶
Before you leave,
在你走以前
you really ought to press charges.
你真的應該去提告。
I'll come with you. 我跟你一起去
I'll go with her. 我跟她去
Thank you very much, Mr. Savelli.
非常感謝您，Savelli 先生
You need a place to stay? 你需要住的地方嗎？
Thanks, but I'm going
to my parents' or my sister's. 謝謝但是我會去我父母或是姐姐那邊
- Where's your family? 你父母家在哪
- A 5 hour drive. 開車五小時
You're up to it? 你要過去嗎？
I'm not taking the car. 我不是說車子
We're still paying the loan. 我們還在付貸款
- Does your family know? 你父母知道了嗎？
- No. 不知道
My sister... sort of. 我姐姐...一點
You have to do it, Miriam. 你必須去做， Miriam。
I'm gonna ask my sister
to pick us up. 我要請我姐來接我們。
Kids, Martine's going to look after you,
孩子們，Martine會看著你們
and then take you to lunch.
然後會帶你們去吃午餐。
What about mom?
媽媽呢？
We have a couple of things to do
我們還有一些事情要做
but we might be back in time.
但是我們會準時回來的。
Come with me? 和我來好嗎？
Julien, get up.
Julien, 走了
Where are your mom's things?
你媽媽的東西在哪邊呢？
Everything OK?
還好嗎？
She's on the phone with her sister.
她跟她姐姐在講電話
The girl told me a little bit.
You knew? 那個女孩告訴了我一些
Not to this extend.
我沒辦法告訴你
So? 怎麼樣？
She's coming with my brother.
They'll be here by 4. 她和我弟會過來，四點會到
OK. What do you want to wear?
好，那你要穿什麼？
What you've got there. 我穿你手上的
I took what I could. 拿我能拿的
Get changed. 去換衣服
Meet me downstairs. 到樓下找我
I'll let Rofia know. 我去跟Rofia講一聲
- Try a little harder. 再試看看
- May I? 可以加入你們嗎？
- Of course. 當然
- Thanks. 謝謝
- Miriam's kids? 是Miriam的孩子們嗎？
- Yes. 是的
Hi, I'm Sophie. 哈囉 我是Sophie
Julien and Josephine.
Julien 和 Josephine.
- Not good? 不好吃？
- No, it's like at school. 不好吃，好像在學校
They could try a little harder. 他們可以再努力點的
You' re not hungry? 你不餓嗎？
She won't see her boyfriend again.
她再也不會看到她的男朋友了
Shut up! OK? 閉嘴好嗎？
Where are you going? 你要去哪裡？
I'm going to the bathroom. 我要去廁所
Hey, none of that. 嘿！不要這樣
OK? 好嗎？
Let's eat. 我們吃吧
Robocop. 機器警察
Robocop? 機器警察？
It's Mrs. Bolocq, our supervisor.
那是我們的主管Bolocq小姐
She acts like a cop 她總是像個警察一樣
so we call her Robocop. 所以我們叫她機器警察
- She has a gun? 她有槍？
I wouldn't be surprised! 哈哈她有我也不驚訝
We've got rifles at my house. 我們家也有槍
They're my dad's. He hunts. 是我爸爸的，他會打獵
Do you go with him? 你會跟他去嗎？
No. He goes with Sally, our dog.
不會，他都跟我們的狗狗Sally去
Sally likes to hunt?
Sally 喜歡打獵嗎？
She barks when dad gets rifle.
當我爸拿著來福槍的時候Sally會大叫
The whole time? 一直叫？
Yeah. 對
She didn't even stop
when he aimed at mom.
連爸爸把槍瞄準媽媽的時候Sally也沒有停止狂吠
Sally's a pretty name.
Sally這名字很美
Where are the kids? 孩子們呢？
On the sofa in the reception. 在前台旁的沙發上
She won't even press charges. 她不肯提告！
Honey... Wake up, 親愛的...起床了
we are leaving soon. 我們要走了喔
Reception. 前台您好
She's right here, I'll send her in.
她在這裡，我讓她進去
Miriam, the accountant is ready for you.
Miriam, 會計準備好在等你囉。
Thanks. 謝謝
I have to do some paperwork, 我有一些文件要處理
I'll be right back. 我等一下就回來
Have a seat. 請坐
Mr. Savelli asked me to do this
as fast as possible.
Savelli先生要我越快處理你的案子越好
You have a new account?
你有新的帳戶了嗎？
Do you have a number?
你有帳號了嗎？
Thanks. 謝謝
Your co-workers
are going to miss their union rep.
你的同事們會想念他們的工會代表的
Read it before you sign.
在簽字之前先讀一下
So what happened?
所以到底發生什麼事了？
What? 什麼？
You getting fire. 你要被解雇了。
I was just wondering what happened.
我只是想知道發生什麼事了
Nothing major. 沒什麼重要的
Let's not got into it. 別提了吧
I just can't stay. 我只是不想待了
It's all very sudden. 這真的很突然
Sorry, I have to answer. 抱歉 我一定要接
I'll be right back. 我馬上回來
- Hi Sylvia. 嗨 Sylvia
- We're here. 我們到了
- Eric's filling up at the gas station. Eric 在加油
- OK 好
Should we meet by the main entrance?
我們要在大門口見嗎？
Call us from the parking lot.
你到停車場打給我們
I'm finishing some paperwork.
我在弄一些書面的東西
Cut it out! 別鬧了
How was the traffic? 塞車有很嚴重嗎
Fine. It'll be busier going back. 不會，可能回程會有點
My phone's almost out of battery. 我手機快沒電了
- Bye. 掰掰
- See you in a bit. 等一下見
Get your stuff. 拿你們的東西
Miriam, come here. Miram 你來一下
Sophie saw your husband
in the store. Sophie 看到你先生在商店裡
It's Sophie. Sophie 打來了
- He's looking for you. 他在找你
- What? 什麼？
He'll see you're not here. 他會發現你不在這裡的
Calm down. 冷靜下來
Stay up there. 你待在那邊不要動
I know. Don't worry. 我知道 別擔心
- He's staring. 他在瞪我
- What's he doing? 他在做什麼？
He's seen me. 他看到我了
He's coming towards me. 他正朝我走來
- Don't look at him. 別看他
- I'm not. 我沒有
Listen. 聽好
Tell him I'm in a staff meeting. 告訴他我在開員工會議
If he insists, 如果他堅持
pretend you're calling me 假裝你打到會議室給我
in the conference room 你就打到 Didier 的辦公室
and call me in Didier's office.
Yes. Bring the receipt. 好的 請將收據帶來
He's there? 他在你旁邊？
It'll be OK, 沒事的，他不知道你在跟我講話
he doesn;t know you're talking to me.
It's going to be fine. 一切都會沒事的
My pleasure. Bye now... 我的榮幸，再見
- Hi Antoine. 哈囉Antoine
- You OK? 你還好嗎？
Where's Miriam? Miriam 在哪裡？
- She's in a staff meeting. 她在開會
- How long will it last? 要開多久
Yeah, a long time. 嗯 非常的久
Damn it! 該死的！
- Shall I take a message? 你要留言嗎？
- I really need to see her. 我需要見到她
It's going to take a while. 但這真的會開很久
- You can't call her? 你不能打給她嗎？
- She's in a meeting. 她在開會
Can you try? It's important. 你不能試試看嗎？
I need two minutes. 這很重要！我只要兩分鐘
Just two minutes. 只要兩分鐘就好了
You've reached Sylvia. 這是Sylvia的答錄機，
Leave a message. I will call you back. 請留言
Sylvia, it's me. He's here. Sylvia 他來了
Idon't know what he wants. 我不知道他想做什麼
Stay at the gas station for now. 你先待在加油站
If he sees you or your car 如果他看到你的車
he'll figure everything out. 他就知道這一切了
Stay put for now. 先不要過來
I'll call you back. 我再打給你
It's Sophie again. Sophie 又打來了
Yes. OK, let me talk to him. 好，好讓我跟他說
Yeah. 喂
What's the matter? 怎麼了？
I went to rent a sander. 我本來要去租拋光機
But I realized you had the checkbook. 但支票簿在你那
I'm in a meeting. 我在開會
Great! What am I supposed to do? 那我該怎麼辦？
I'll bring it to you. 我拿過去給你
What does he want? 他要什麼？
No, mom! Don't go! 不要！媽媽！不要走！
Julien, calm down. Julien，冷靜下來
No! Don't go! 不要！不要走！
Josephine, take your brother! Josephine 抓好你弟
Miriam, you need to take Miriam，你得把家務事
your problems elsewhere. 帶離這裡
He needs the checkbook. 他只要支票簿
Does he suspect something? 他有察覺任何事情嗎？
- Should I come too? 我要跟著去嗎？
- No! 不要！
Call Eric and Sylvia. 打給Eric 和 Sylvia
They must wait. 他們一定要等
Your name tag! 你的名牌！
Hi. 嗨
I forgot, I'm sorry. 我忘了 對不起
You working Friday? 你禮拜五要上班？
Yes. Why? 對，為什麼？
They changed my schemdule. 他們改了我的班表
I have to work, 我要上班了，我沒辦法去
I can't go to Julien's class meeting. Julien的家長會
Friday? I'll manage. 禮拜五嗎？ 我會去
Mrs. Besson? Besson女士？
You weren't here this morning. 你今早不在阿
Hello. 你好
Yes I was. 我在阿。
My colleague 我同事帶了你的班ㄟ
will handle your return.
Thanks. 謝謝
Clara had to replace you Clara 在21號櫃檯
at register 21. 幫你帶班ㄟ
I was helping in children's clothing. 我剛在童裝部
- You left your register. 你離開你的櫃
- A void at cashier 17. 17號櫃有要退貨
- That's Gaëlle’s job 那也是Gaëlle的工作阿
- She's on break. 她在休假
She's going to get an earful 她會聽到我
from me. 不停碎唸她的名字的
See you tonight. 那今晚見了
I have to go back up. 我要回去了
I want to talk to you. 我想跟你說一下話
What time is your break? 你什麼時候休息？
It depends on the meeting. 這真的要看我的會
I'll wait here, 我在這裡等
call me when you're done. 你好了打給我
OK, but it depends... 好，再說吧...
Excuse me. Warranties? 請問保固哪裡辦理？
- At the service desk, ma'am. 在服務台，女士
- Thank you. 謝謝你
He's still in the store. 他還在店裡 我們現在就走
We have to go now. Your coat! 你的外套！
- The uniform. 制服
- What? 什麼？
We need the uniform back. 我們需要把制服拿回來
Fuck. 幹
Sophie, it's Gaëlle. Sophie, 我是 Gaëlle.
Where is he? 他在哪裡？
I haven't seen him leave. 我沒看到他走
He must be walking around. 他一定在亂晃
Come on! 來吧！
Didier!
Let's go. 我們走吧
Wait here, I'll go to take a look. 在這裡等著，
我去看一下
Walk normally. 正常的走
It's clear, I didn't see him. 沒事 我沒看到他
Come on! 快點！
He's there! 他在那邊！
Are you leaving? 你要走了嗎？
Yes. 對