Sally!
Be good.
Where are you going?
I have to get some cigarettes for my dad.
Hurry then Julien.
We have a test this morning.
By the way, are your parents coming
to the class meeting on Friday?
Hurry up!
Put your seatbelt on, please.
Did you get my cigaretters?
Thanks.
Hi Miriam.
Didier, can I leave the kids with you?
- What's going on?
- I won't be long.
Of course.
What's the rush?
Register 2 at noon, register 3...
- Alarm didn't go off?
- Car trouble again.
I need to talk to Gaëlle.
- Hang on.
- Can I talk to you a minute?
Sorry.
I'm handing you over to Rofia.
There's a void at Fatou’s register.
- Ask Robocop.
- She's not in yet.
I'll be quick. Wait for me here.
- In the locker room?
- OK.
What's going on?
- I need to see Savelli.
- He's in a meeting.
- I brought the kids.
- What?
I don't know what to do.
I must get out quick.
It's going to be fine.
It's not a big deal.
Ask Rofia.
I have to do something.
You choose... It's simple.
You choose... Wait, I'll show you.
Choose a weapon: a sword...
Hi kids.
Everything alright, Didier?
Great.
And that's your score.
She has a fever.
I'm waiting for the doctor.
I'll let you know.
Thank you. Bye.
Ah... Miriam.
Tell them I'll only be a minute.
I'm sorry to take your time.
It's short notice but Gaëlle explained.
How shall we proceed?
I have no idea.
Do you want to take some time?
Maybe a leave?
No that's impossible I can't come back after
all that…
- Have you pressed charges?
- No.
You should press charges.
You'll need a medical certificate
for your file.
It's just that...
I've got the kids
and we must leave quickly.
It would be great,
but Idon't have time.
I see.
You're really leaving then?
I'm in no rush to see you go!
I can fire you
so you get your benefits.
But you'll have to come back
for an interview.
Yes, I know.
Do you have a new address?
I'm leaving town,
until things calm down.
I don't know where I'm going yet.
We have two moths to do the interview.
That's great...
It's just... I'm sorry but...
if I have to wait...
What I mean is...
I'm going to need money.
No it's fine...
I'll give you my parents' address.
Accounting will give you an advance.
You can unblock the interest
on your shared profits.
- For the rest, we'll do like we said.
- Thank you.
I need to open my own account.
Before you leave,
you really ought to press charges.
I'll come with you.
I'll go with her.
Thank you very much, Mr. Savelli.
You need a place to stay?
Thanks, but I'm going
to my parents' or my sister's.
- Where's your family?
- A 5 hour drive.
You're up to it?
I'm not taking the car.
We're still paying the loan.
- Does your family know?
- No.
My sister... sort of.
You have to do it, Miriam.
I'm gonna ask my sister
to pick us up.
Kids, Martine's going
to look after you,
and then take you to lunch.
What about mom?
We have a couple of things to do
but we might be back in time.
Come with me?
Julien, get up.
Where are your mom's things?
Everything OK?
She's on the phone with her sister.
The girl told me a little bit.
You knew?
Not to this extend.
So?
She's coming with my brother.
They'll be here by 4.
OK. What do you want to wear?
What you've got there.
I took what I could.
Get changed.
Meet me downstairs.
I'll let Rofia know.
- Try a little harder.
- May I?
- Of course.
- Thanks.
- Miriam's kids?
- Yes.
Hi, I'm Sophie.
Julien and Josephine.
- Not good?
- No, it's like at school.
They could try a little harder.
You' re not hungry?
She won't see her boyfriend again.
Shut up! OK?
Where are you going?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Hey, none of that.
OK?
Let's eat.
Robocop.
Robocop?
It's Mrs. Bolocq, our supervisor.
She acts like a cop
so we call her Robocop.
- She has a gun?
I wouldn't be surprised!
We've got rifles at my house.
They're my dad's. He hunts.
Do you go with him?
No. He goes with Sally, our dog.
Sally likes to hunt?
She barks when dad gets rifle.
The whole time?
Yeah.
She didn't even stop
when he aimed at mom.
Sally's a pretty name.
Where are the kids?
On the sofa in the reception.
She won't even press charges.
Honey... Wake up,
we are living soon.
Reception.
She's right here, I'll send her in.
Miriam, the accountant is ready for you.
Thanks.
I have to do some paperwork,
I'll be right back.
Have a seat.
Mr. Savelli asked me to do this
as fast as possible.
You have a new account?
Do you have a number?
Thanks.
Your co-workers
are going to miss their union rep.
Read it before you sign.
So what happened?
What?
You getting fire.
I was just wondering what happened.
Nothing major.
Let's not got into it.
I just can't stay.
It's all very sudden.
Sorry, I have to answer.
I'll be right back.
- Hi Sylvia.
- We're here.
- Eric's filling up at the gas station.
- OK
Should we meet by the main entrance?
Call us from the parking lot.
I'm finishing some paperwork.
Cut it out!
How was the traffic?
Fine. It'll be busier going back.
My phone's almost out of battery.
- Bye.
- See you in a bit.
Get your stuff.
Miriam, come here.
Sophie saw your husband
in the store.
It's Sophie.
- He's looking for you.
- What?
He'll see you're not here.
Calm down.
Stay up there.
I know. Don't worry.
- He's staring.
- What's he doing?
He's seen me.
He's coming towards me.
- Don't look at him.
- I'm not.
Listen.
Tell him I'm in a staff meeting.
If he insists,
pretend you're calling me
in the conference room
and call me in Didier's office.
Yes. Bring the receipt.
He's there?
It'll be OK,
he doesn;t know you're talking to me.
It's going to be fine.
My pleasure. Bye now...
- Hi Antoine.
- You OK?
Where's Miriam?
- She's in a staff meeting.
- How long will it last?
Yeah, a long time.
Damn it!
- Shall I take a message?
- I really need to see her.
It's going to take a while.
- You can't call her?
- She's in a meeting.
Can you try? It's important.
I need two minutes.
Just two minutes.
You've reached Sylvia.
Leave a message. I will call you back.
Sylvia, it's me. He's here.
Idon't know what he wants.
Stay at the gas station for now.
If he sees you or your car
he'll figure everything out.
Stay put for now.
I'll call you back.
It's Sophie again.
Yes. OK, let me talk to him.
Yeah.
What's the matter?
I went to rent a sander.
But I realised you had the checkbook.
I'm in a meeting.
Great! What am I supposed to do?
I'll bring it to you.
What does he want?
No, mom! Don't go!
Julien, calm down.
No! Don't go!
Josephine, take your brother!
Miriam, you need to take
your problems elsewhere.
He needs the checkbook.
Does he suspect something?
- Should I come too?
- No!
Call Eric and Sylvia.
They must wait.
Your name tag!
Hi.
I forgot, I'm sorry.
You working Friday?
Yes. Why?
They changed my schemdule.
I have to work,
I can't go to Julien's class meeting.
Friday? I'll manage.
Mrs. Besson?
You weren't here this morning.
Hello.
Yes I was.
My colleague
will handle your return.
Thanks.
Clara had to replace you
at register 21.
I was helping in children's clothing.
- You left your register.
- A void at cashier 17.
- That's Gaëlle’s job
- She's on break.
She's going to get an earful
from me.
See you tonight.
I have to go back up.
I want to talk to you.
What time is your break?
It depends on the meeting.
I'll wait here,
call me when you're done.
OK, but it depends...
Excuse me. Warranties?
- At the service desk, ma'am.
- Thank you.
He's still in the store.
We have to go now. Your coat!
- The uniform.
- What?
We need the uniform back.
Fuck.
Sophie, it's Gaëlle.
Where is he?
I haven't seen him leave.
He must be walking around.
Come on1!
Didier!
Let's go.
Wait here, I'll go to take a look.
Walk normally.
It's clear, I didn't see him.
Come on!
He's there!
Are you leaving?
Yes.